Guide to the Wright H. Everett Papers, 1853-1998 and undated RL.00376
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Wright H. Everett papers
1853-1998 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Everett, Wright
RL.00376
27 Linear Feet
Wright H. Bill Everett (1925-2010) was a media space salesman for several major magazines, and the founder of his own businesses, Flix and the W.H. Everett Co., that specialized in a variety of print materials combining humorous captions with still images from silent movies. The Wright H. Everett Papers span the years 1853-1998 and include correspondence, photographs and negatives, 8mm and 16mm films and audiotapes, print advertisements, layouts, presentations, research reports, pamphlets and brochures that document Everett's career selling advertising space in national magazines as well as his own businesses, Flix and the W.H. Everett Co. Magazines represented in the collection include Advertising Age, American Home, Flying, Progressive Grocer, Reader's Digest, Reminisce, Suburbia Today, Time, Western Advertising and Woman's Home Companion. Other companies represented include American Greeting Cards, Hunter Snead, Lennen-Newell, Maclean Hunter Media and Remington Advertising. There are also files relating to Everett's book How Were Things At The Office? Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
11,000 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Wright H. Everett Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2011.
Biographical Note
Chronology List
1925 Aug. 23 Born,
1939-1942 Attended Hackley School, Tarrytown, N.Y.
1943 Attended Staunton Military Academy, Staunton, Va.
1943-1946, 1950 Military service, U.S. Army Air Force
1944 Aviation Cadet, U.S. Army Air Force
1946-1948 Student, Journalism major, Kent State University, Kent, Oh.
1948-1950 Merchandising, Young & Rubicam
1950-1951 Advertising Promotion Manager, Sports Afield magazine
1950-1956 Advertising Sales, Woman's Home Companion magazine
1952-1953 Free-lance artist and writer, Flying magazine
1953 Advertising assistant, Hunting & Fishing magazine
1956 Advertising assistant, General Outdoor Advertising
1956-1960 Advertising Sales, American Home magazine
1959 Publication of How Were Things at the Office?
1960-1963 Self-employed, W.H. Everett Co.
1961 Produced humorous image series, So You're in the Ad Game?, Marketing magazine
1962-1970 Produced humorous image series, What They're (Really) Saying, Advertising Age
1963-1965 Advertising Sales Development, Time magazine
1965-circa 1985 Advertising Sales, Progressive Grocer magazine
2010 Aug. 30 Died, Ridgefield, Conn.
Collection Overview
The Wright H. Everett Papers span the years 1853-1998 and include correspondence, photographs and negatives, 8mm and 16mm films and audio tapes, print advertisements, layouts, presentations, research reports, pamphlets and brochures that document Everett's career selling advertising space in national magazines as well as his own businesses, Flix and the W.H. Everett Co. Magazines represented in the collection include Advertising Age, American Home, Flying, Progressive Grocer, Reader's Digest, Reminisce, Suburbia Today, Time, Western Advertising and Woman's Home Companion. Other companies represented include American Greeting Cards, Hunter Snead, Lennen-Newell, MacLean Hunter Media and Remington Advertising. There are also files relating to Everett's book How Were Things At The Office?
Collection Arrangement
Collection is arranged into four Series: Personal Files; Business Files; Oversize Materials; and Audiovisual Materials.
Separated Material
The following items have been removed from the collection to be cataloged separately:
Applebaum, Stanley. Old Time Woodcuts from the Nineteenth-Century Stage. 1977. New York: Dover Publications.
Bettger, Frank. How I Raised Myself from Failure to Success in Selling. 1949. New York: Prentice-Hall.
Carey, Gary. Lost Films. 1970. New York: Museum of Modern Art.
Franklin, Joe. Classics of the Silent Screen. 1959. New York: Citadel Press.
Gillispie, Charles C., Ed. A Diderot Pictorial Encyclopedia of Trades and Industry. 2 volumes. 1959, 1987. New York: Dover Publications.
Grafton, Carol Belanger. Old-Fashioned Eating and Drinking Illustrations. 1988. New York: Dover Publications.
Grafton, Carol Belanger. Trades and Occupations. 1990. New York: Dover Publications.
Griffith, Richard, and Mayer, Arthur. The Movies. 1957, 1970. New York: Simon & Schuster.
Harper's New Monthly Magazine. 1890. Bound Volume XXV, June-November 1862.
Harter, Jim. Food and Drink: A Pictorial Archive from Nineteenth-Century Sources. 3rd edition. 1983. New York: Dover Publications.
Hodgins, Eric. Enough Time? The Patterns of Executive Life. 1959. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday & Company.
Hornung, Clarence P. Handbook of Early Advertising Art. 3rd edition. 1956. New York: Dover Publications.
Jones, Edgar R. Those Were The Good Old Days: A Happy Look at American Advertising, 1880-1950. 1959, 1979. New York: Simon & Schuster.
Meyers, Warren B. Who Is That? The Late Late Viewers Guide to the Old Old Movies. 1967. New York: Personality Posters.
Paper, C. A Case of Humor. Edited by Jackie Kannon. 1961. New York: Kanrom Inc.
Related Material
Related material may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Bill Communications Sales and Marketing Management Vertical Files
Charles W. Hoyt Company Records
Irving Sonn Papers
J. Walter Thompson Company Marketing Vertical Files
McGraw-Hill Marketing Information Center Vertical File
Wit and humor in advertising -- United States; Wit and humor in advertising; Selling -- United States; Selling; Sales promotion -- United States; Sales promotion; Advertising executives -- United States; Advertising executives; 8mm; Wit and humor in business -- United States; Wit and humor in business; Negatives (photographic); 16mm; Advertising -- United States; Audiotapes; Photographs; Time, Inc.; Reader's Digest Association; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Everett, Wright; Everett, Wright; American Greeting Card Co
- Personal Files, 1946-1965 and undated, 1 box
  - Biographical information, 1936-1965 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Writings and clippings from Kent State, 1946-1948 (Box 1)
- Business Files, 1853-1998 and undated, 27 boxes
  - Advertising Age (Other items in Oversize Materials) (Box 1)
    - Booklet, What They're (Really) Saying, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Clippings, What They're (Really) Saying, 1962-1967 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1960-1966 (Box 1)
  - Advertising agencies, general information, 1957-1962 (Box 1)
  - American Greetings
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1964-1981 (Box 1)
    - Samples, undated (Box 1)
  - American Home (Other items in Oversize Materials)
    - Advertising orders, 1957-1959 (Box 1)
    - Advertising proposal for Cunningham & Walsh/Texaco, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Advertising proposal for McCann-Erickson/Esso, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 2)
    - Proposal for Esso, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Charles H. Clark correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 2)
  - Clippings
    - Glick Brothers, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1952-1993 (Box 2)
  - Contacts, business cards, etc., 1961, 1 of 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Contacts, business cards, etc. (continued), 1961, 2 of 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Crowell-Collier, 1952-1964 (Box 3)
  - Creative Enterprises, logo designs, undated (Box 3)
  - Design, woodcuts, undated (Box 3)
  - Diamond Match
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Samples, undated (Box 3)
  - Drawings
    - By Everett, 1944 (Box 3)
    - By McKeon/Everett, undated (Box 3)
  - Esso advertising, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Flix (Other items in Oversize Materials)
    - Brown & Bigelow, 1960-1965 (Box 3)
    - Business plan, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Catalog orders, not paid, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Catalog orders, paid, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
    - Copy lines, undated (Box 4)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1960-1976 (Box 4)
    - Design, cartoon, undated (Box 4)
    - Direct marketing, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Edson Foster, County Beach Resort, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Esquire shoe polish, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Fletcher Richards, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Invoices, 1961-1966 (Box 5)
    - Invoices (continued), 1961-1966 (Box 6)
    - Legal, 1960-1962 (Box 6)
    - Lennen-Newell, 1961 (Box 6)
    - Promotion
      - Catalog, undated (Box 6)
      - Design and artwork, undated (Box 6)
      - House advertisement, 1963 (Box 6)
      - Logos and stationery, undated (Box 6)
    - Portfolio of sample print advertisements, 1964-1967 (Box 6)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 6)
    - Rumrill, undated (Box 6)
    - Samples (Box 7)
      - Booklet designs, undated (Box 7)
      - Booklets
        - Ackerman Associates, Clients' Progress Report, 1962 (Box 7)
        - Avis, Convention Capers, circa 1963 (Box 7)
        - Brown & Bigelow, Inside Business, undated (Box 7)
        - Brown & Bigelow, Hocus Pocus, undated (Box 7)
        - Bulova, A Funny Thing Could Happen To You, undated (Box 7)
        - Emery Air Freight, Auto-Mated Service, undated (Box 7)
        - General Electric Credit Corporation (GECC), Weren't You Once My Customer?, circa 1968 (Box 7)
        - Harold's Club, appointment calendar, 1968 (Box 7)
        - Kankakee Federal Savings and Loan, Home Buyers Want To Know, undated (Box 7)
        - Knox Gelatine, Our Memory Book, undated (Box 7)
        - Martin Caiden and Hank Curth, The Inside Story of NASA, 1962 (Box 7)
        - Mr. Paul, Kookie Kaptions, 1962 (Box 7)
        - Ohio Brass Co., check, 1962 (Box 7)
        - Parade Magazine, Who's Afraid of the Summer Slump?, undated (Box 7)
        - Pitney-Bowes, Office Mail-O-Drama, undated (Box 7)
        - Price Stern Sloan, pamphlet no. 1, undated (Box 7)
        - Schneider Oil, Progress Report, 1960 (Box 7)
        - Standard Rate and Data Service, The Chase, 1980 (Box 7)
        - Standard Rate and Data Service, They Lurk in the Shadows, undated (Box 7)
        - Suburbia Today, Advertisers Demand to Know, undated (Box 7)
      - Captioned images, undated (Other items in Oversize Materials) (Box 7)
      - Greeting cards (Box 8)
        - Flix, undated (Box 8)
        - Other, undated (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous designs, undated (Box 8)
      - Postcard designs, undated (Box 8)
      - Postcards, 1962-1993 (Box 8)
      - Print and direct mail advertising, undated (Box 8)
    - Stationery, note pads, etc., undated (Box 8)
    - Trade cards, undated (Box 8)
    - Trade cards (continued), undated (Box 9)
    - TV Guide, TV Jibe Flicker Snickers, 1964-1969 (Box 9)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 9)
    - Scrapbook, image portfolio, undated (Box 10)
  - Flying Magazine, 1951-1953 (Box 10)
  - Hallmark Cards, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
  - How Were Things At The Office?
    - General, 1960-1965 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1959-1972 (Box 10)
    - Images, circa 1959 (Box 10)
    - Paid orders, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Publication, 1959-1963 (Box 10)
    - Scrapbook of testimonial letters, 1959-1960 (Box 10)
    - Scrapbook of testimonial letters (continued), 1959-1960 (Box 11)
    - WOR broadcast transcript, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Hunter Snead files
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1939-1962 (Box 11)
    - Printer's Ink clippings, The Sale I Never Forgot, undated (Box 11)
    - Scrapbook of antique sales materials, 1866-1890 (Box 11)
  - McCall's Magazine, 1957-1965 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958-1965 (Box 11)
  - Mullahy Company, freelance news release, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Nucleonics Magazine, 1963 (Box 11)
  - Photographs (Other items in Oversize Materials)
    - Booklet layout, undated (Box 12)
    - Captioned images, undated (Box 12)
    - Media booklet, undated (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 12)
    - Movie stills, undated (Box 12)
    - People, undated (Box 12)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 12)
    - Slides, undated (Box 13)
    - Stereographs, undated (Box 13)
    - Workshop, undated (Box 13)
  - Presentation scripts, various projects, undated (Box 14)
  - Printed Material
    - Booklets
      - Ambassador Hotel, Convention Center of the West, undated (Box 14)
      - American Salesman, 1962 Aug. (Box 14)
      - Analog Magazine, 1964 Jan. (Box 14)
      - Bernäd Creations, The Best of Bernäd, 1959 (Box 14)
      - Butterick & Co., Catalogue for Winter, 1874 (Box 14)
      - CBS directory, 1963 Jan. (Box 14)
      - Civic Theatre Guild, Come Alive program guide, 1964 (Box 14)
      - Commercial Credit Plan, Successful Salesmen, 1963-1965 (Box 14)
      - Dover Catalog of Photography and Film Books, undated (Box 14)
      - Elmer Wheeler, How to Sell When Selling Is Tough, 1958 (Box 14)
      - Emery Air Freight, Auto-Mated Service, undated (Box 14)
      - Francis W. Hatch Awards brochure, undated (Box 14)
      - Gerald Gardner, I'm In Charge Here, 1968 (Box 15)
      - Gerald Gardner, Who's In Charge Here?, 1980 (Box 15)
      - Godey's Lady's Book, 1853 Oct. (Box 15)
      - Good Impressions Rubber Stamp Catalogue, 1992 (Box 15)
      - Harness, World's Fair Special Souvenir Number, 1893 (Box 15)
      - J. Thomas McCarthy, The Rights of Publicity and Privacy, 1989 (Box 15)
      - John Martin's Book, 1917 June (Box 15)
      - Kinney Car Leasing, If You Own Your Car, undated (Box 15)
      - Lippencott & Marguries, Design Sense 22, undated (Box 15)
      - Madison Avenue, 1959 Dec. (Box 15)
      - Magazine Industry Newsletter, 1964 Mar. 28 (Box 15)
      - Marketing Information Group, 1963 (Box 15)
      - Mel Richman, Inc., Image #3, 1960 Spring (Box 15)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Emblems of Unity and Freedom, undated (Box 15)
      - Mid-America Publishing, New 5-Step Plan to Coordinated Selling, 1964 (Box 15)
      - Myron Johnson, American Advertising 1800-1900, undated (Box 15)
      - National Sales Development Institute, Cold Call Selling, undated (Box 15)
      - National Sales Development Institute, Listen, 1959 (Box 15)
      - National Systems Corporation, Annual Report, 1963 (Box 15)
      - Presentation Designers, Visual Selling, undated (Box 15)
      - Promo Magazine, 1993 June (Box 15)
      - Saints and Sinners French Lexicon, undated (Box 15)
      - Southern Advertising and Publishing, 1959 Nov. (Box 16)
      - Stan Lee, Monsters To Laugh With, 1965 (Box 16)
      - Suburbia Today, Suburbia Far Out, 1960 (Box 16)
      - Taylor/Merchant, Sell On Sight Idea Kit, undated (Box 16)
      - The Child's Companion, circa 1872 (Box 16)
      - The Salesman, 1959 (Box 16)
      - Time, Cartoon Book, 1963 (Box 16)
      - Time, The Old Taylor Salesman's Coloring Book, undated (Box 16)
      - Time, Why Advertise?, 1958 (Box 16)
      - Traffic World, Tickler, circa 1965 (Box 16)
      - Ward, Lock & Co., Illustrated Gift Books, undated (Box 16)
      - W.C. Fields, I Never Met a Kid I Liked, 1970 (Box 16)
      - Western International Media Promotion Broadcast Services, undated (Box 16)
    - Cartoon, Selectivity As Portrayed By Cobean, undated (Box 16)
    - Cookbooks
      - Church & Dwight, Cow Brand Soda Cookbook, 1900 (Box 16)
      - Lydia Pinkham, Food and Health, circa 1920 (Box 16)
      - Lydia Pinkham, Practical Cooking Recipes, circa 1920 (Box 16)
      - Mrs. Winslow's Domestic Cookbook, 1874 (Box 16)
      - Procter & Gamble, 12 Dozen Time-Saving Recipes, 1932 (Box 16)
    - McCall Company, Spirit Magazine, 1930 May (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 16)
    - Postcards, 1905-1962 and undated (Box 16)
    - Presentation, Show and Tell Productions, Johns-Manville Sales Corporation, 1966 (Box 16)
    - Trade cards, 1879-1981 and undated (Box 17)
    - Trade cards, Economics Press Sales Ticklers, undated (Box 17)
    - W. Gold & Son & Daughter, Inc., Gags--Gadgets--Gifts catalog, undated (Box 17)
  - Progressive Grocer (Other items in Oversize Materials)
    - Cartoon by Everett, undated (Box 17)
    - Correspondence (Box 17)
    - All-World Photos, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Procter & Gamble, 1963-1965 (Box 17)
    - Food Industry Forum, circa 1986 (Box 17)
    - Info-Source Library Service, undated (Box 17)
    - MacLean Hunter Media, 1988-1991 (Other items in Oversize Materials) (Box 17)
    - Marketing and Media Guide, 1993 (Box 18)
    - Memoranda, 1964-1993 (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1993 and undated (Box 18)
    - Presentation scripts, 1965-1985 and undated (Box 18)
    - Promotional cards, 1970-1991 and undated (Box 18)
    - Promotional flyers, 1985-1992 and undated (Box 18)
    - Publications
      - Colonial Stores study, circa 1963 (Box 18)
      - Dillon study, 1960 (Box 18)
      - Facts and Fallacies in Selling Grocery Products, undated (Box 18)
      - Food & Drink Spot Illustrations, 1982 (Box 18)
      - Food Business, 1993 June 14 (Box 18)
      - Food Service Supermarkets, 1990 (Box 19)
      - Glossary of Grocery Industry Terms, 1995 (Box 19)
      - Invention and Technology, 1994 Spring (Box 19)
      - It's a Crazy Business, 1963 (Box 19)
      - It's Still a Crazy Business, 1973 (Box 19)
      - Life and Times of Progressive Grocer, 1987 (Box 19)
      - Progressive Grover, reprint of first issue, 1922 (Box 19)
      - Progressive Grocer, 1972-1998 (Box 19)
      - The Merchandisers, 1989 (Box 19)
      - You Have a Nice Supermarket Here But I Can't Find Anything, 1973 (Box 19)
    - Revenue report, 1965-1985 (Box 19)
    - Space and net revenue statements, 1973-1976 (Box 19)
    - Wall plaque, undated (Box 19)
  - Reminisce Magazine
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995-1996 and undated (Box 20)
    - Submitted article, I Discovered Life on Mars in 1938, 1996 (Box 20)
  - Schine Enterprises, 1960-1964 and undated (Box 20)
  - Suburbia Today, 1961-1963 and undated (Other items in Oversize Materials) (Box 20)
  - Time, Inc. (Other items in Oversize Materials)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1963-1964 and undated (Box 20)
    - Presentations
      - Aerojet-General, 1964 (Box 21)
      - Aerospace, 1963-1964 and undated (Box 21)
      - Airline travel, 1964 and undated (Box 21)
      - Avis Rent-a-Car, 1964 and undated (Box 21)
      - Canadian tourism, undated (Box 21)
      - Thrifty Rent-a-Car, 1964 (Box 21)
      - Travel market, 1963 (Box 21)
    - Promotional
      - Hilton Hotels merchandising, 1964 (Other items in Oversize Materials) (Box 21)
      - National Car Rental, 1964-1965 (Box 21)
      - Various designs, undated (Box 21)
      - Various flyers, 1963 and undated (Box 21)
    - Proposal for Time, 1962 (Box 21)
    - Publications
      - 1964 Election Year Argument Settler, 1964 (Box 22)
      - Miscellaneous travel-related publications, 1952-1963 (Box 22)
      - Report for Piper Aircraft, 1964 (Box 22)
      - Time, first issue, 1923 (Box 22)
  - Western Advertising, 1964-1965 (Box 22)
  - W.H. Everett Co.
    - A.C. Nielsen, 1961 (Box 22)
    - Advertising Age, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Al Paul Lefton Company, 1961 (Box 22)
    - Alex Smith, 1961 (Box 22)
    - Animators, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Atlantic Bernstein, undated (Box 22)
    - Banning Repplier, 1961 (Box 22)
    - BBDO, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Bernäd Creations, 1959 (Box 22)
    - Biddle Company, 1962 (Box 23)
    - Bill Geeslin (De Soto Festival), 1962 (Box 23)
    - Blue Cross, undated (Box 23)
    - Business proposal, undated (Box 23)
    - Campbell-Mithun, 1961 (Box 23)
    - Catalog of Early Movie Photos, undated (Box 23)
    - Charles W. Hoyt Company, 1962 (Box 23)
    - Clippings, announcement of business, 1962 (Box 23)
    - Cohn-Hall-Marx, undated (Box 23)
    - Columbia Records proposal, 1962 (Box 23)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1976 and undated (Box 23)
    - Craigle & Paulson, 1962 (Box 23)
    - Creative examples
      - Annual Report, 1961 (Box 23)
      - Company Policy, undated (Box 23)
      - Looking for Something New in Illustrations?, undated (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 23)
      - Monkey Business, undated (Box 24)
    - Curtis Publishing, 1962 (Box 24)
    - Davidson Publishing, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Diamond Match, 1962 (Box 24)
    - Dodge dealers, 1963 (Box 24)
    - F.H. Hayhurst Co., 1961 (Box 24)
    - Film commercials, 1960-1961 and undated (Box 24)
    - Finance and miscellaneous, 1964-1980 and undated (Box 24)
    - Finances, 1962-1963 (Box 24)
    - First Advertising Agency Group, 1962 (Box 24)
    - General Outdoor Advertising, 1963 and undated (Box 24)
    - Grant Advertising, 1961 (Box 24)
    - Guarantees, etc., undated (Box 24)
    - Hilton Hotels, 1959-1963 and undated (Box 24)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1961 (Box 25)
    - Kastor, Hilton, Chesley, Clifford & Atherton, Inc., 1963 (Box 25)
    - Kellogg's, plastic fort promotion, undated (Box 25)
    - Lea & Perrins, 1960 (Box 25)
    - Ledger, 1960-1967 (Box 25)
    - Leo Burnett, 1961 (Box 25)
    - Liggett & Myers, undated (Box 25)
    - McCann-Erickson, undated (Box 25)
    - McCann-Marschalk, 1962 (Box 25)
    - MacLean Hunter Media, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Metropolitan Life, 1962 (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous copy, 1964 and undated (Box 25)
    - Nestlé, undated (Box 25)
    - Outline of business and potential as of 8/27/62, 1962 (Box 25)
    - Parker Vanguard pen proposal, undated (Box 25)
    - Pepsi-Cola, 1961-1963 (Box 25)
    - Perfect Secretary, book notes and correspondence, 1962-1963 and undated (Box 25)
    - Perlin Products, 1962 (Box 25)
    - Project X, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Promotional materials, undated (Box 25)
    - Proposal for gasoline promotion, 1960 (Box 25)
    - Prospects and contacts, 1960 and undated (Box 25)
    - Prospects list, 1964 (Box 25)
    - Publicity, 1962 (Box 25)
    - Reader's Digest, 1962 (Other items in Oversize Materials) (Box 25)
    - Remington Advertising, 1962 and undated (Box 26)
    - Remington Advertising--zinc printing plates, undated (Box 26)
    - Report and prospectus, 1962 (Box 26)
    - Revell, Inc., 1960 (Box 26)
    - Robert Zulauf, 1962 (Box 26)
    - Robotham Advertising, 1960-1962 (Box 26)
    - Sales, 1960-1962 (Box 26)
    - Schine Enterprises, 1962 (Box 26)
    - Seagram Distillers, 1961 (Box 26)
    - Sherle Maquire (Micmac Inc.), 1962 (Box 26)
    - Shoe Box packaging toy/item proposal, 1962 (Box 26)
    - Sources and suppliers, 1962-1976 (Box 26)
    - Stern Walters & Simmons, 1961 (Box 26)
    - Ted Bates, 1962 (Box 26)
    - 3M presentation, 1962 (Box 26)
    - U.S. Gypsum Co., 1963 (Box 26)
    - U.S. Rubber (Keds), undated (Box 26)
    - Van Sant Dugdale, 1960 (Box 26)
    - Victor Adding Machine Co., 1962 (Box 27)
    - Western Union proposal, 1962 (Box 27)
    - WHN, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Work file, 1960 and undated (Box 27)
  - Woman's Day, 1961 (Box 27)
  - Woman's Home Companion (Other items in Oversize Materials)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1957 (Box 27)
    - Packaged Promotions for Women's Clubs (binder)circa 1955 (Box 27)
    - Proposal for regional advertising, 1954 (Box 27)
  - Memorabilia
    - Arm band, 26 Julio, undated (Box 28)
    - Arm band, U.S.S. Maine, undated (Box 28)
    - Button, S.O.S.--Stamp Out Stockouts, undated (Box 28)
    - Button, Bill--William Howard Taft, undated (Box 28)
    - Coffee mug, But what have you done for me lately?, undated (Box 28)